<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Temperature 0.5 on SAIGE</title>
    <link>https://saige.netlify.app/tags/temperature-0.5/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Temperature 0.5 on SAIGE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://saige.netlify.app/tags/temperature-0.5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I am the one who is not a fan of the Tribunal. I have never had any great moral concerns to share about this damn thing. The fact is that it is a pretty good guild. I am not one to let too many people in at the T.V. Club. The members are paid a living like any other, but there is a tiny membership fee of just under twenty-five dollars a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always desired to be able to say what I say without having to explain it. I have always been interested in the question: what does the term &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; even mean in practice? And yet, until now, I had never heard anyone speak in such generalities about the nature of the enemy. Now there were two professors of political science who were absolutely abysmal when it came to demonizing Jew sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
The second of the three episodes of the &amp;ldquo;Veil of the Republic,&amp;rdquo; in which Surrealism succeeds in ridding the world of it, &amp;ldquo;Veil of the Republic&amp;rdquo; is as dead as its first movie, in which the moral as well as the practical importance of liberty is taught. In this terrible historical drama, which succeeds only in giving the impression of an intellectual history, &amp;ldquo;Prisoners of the World&amp;rdquo; loses without real cause a great number of qualities that make it different from the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I am a woman.
I am a woman who has closed my eyes.
I am a woman who has closed them again.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are cold.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are heavy.
All the doors of paradise slam shut.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are heavy.
And I am a woman who has closed them again.
A man.
He is absent-minded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
The man with the long beard was standing at the entrance of the café. He made a mental note to get to the back of the building. The man with the long beard was sitting at the far end of the sidewalk. He spoke: &amp;ldquo;I have a gig, I swear. I&#39;ll have a meal out of this here. Five francs and ten florins is a good meal for a boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
I have never understood the desire of certain of those who follow me to express themselves. Desire, yes, but also a great deal more. They are looking for something specific, something that can reproduce what has already occurred, something that can be repeated, something that can be passed from one taste to another, something to be experienced by the senses. Here we are, in front of a live camera, capturing an extraordinary display of this desire: the subject is Engels&amp;rsquo; The Communist Manifesto (1875), directedquely by an avowed anti-Communist, the title The Party which Spoke (1875) given its full, unedited glory, and presented in full color, with the same organization and tactics adopted by Rigaud&#39;s and Engels&amp;rsquo; other Manifesto texts, the same dedication, the same style of poetic expression, the same methods of propaganda?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
The world’s most celebrated psychiatrist has just died. He was 80 years old. His final words to me were these: &amp;ldquo;My illness, my illness&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; If I must wait to be treated in a hospital again, I know that my fate will be in that same building. I am in the offing. I am just one day away from telling my story. I hope it is told in the manner that your mother told it to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have seen Mr. and Mrs. Newland walk from shop to shop, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose. And yet, I was told, they went their separate ways. I was taught that the old lady was the last to be discovered, and that the old lady was found the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
There are two or three reasons why the most experienced and devoted fans of Marvel&#39;s The Avengers would not go out of their way to try and kill each other. The first is that, like Captain America, they love to compete. But they also love to compete on a huge and gratifying level. They are the savants of the universe. And they are relentless. I have never seen such a determined and devoted lover on display in my life-like time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ======================================== The sun is always on my left. I leave this area, which is only a few hundred meters from the main road. I go toward the house of the taxi-seller. He is on my right. I say: &amp;ldquo;The house on your left is yours. I&#39;ll go meet Nadja.&amp;rdquo; Nadja is waiting for me at the corner of the Rue Lafayette and the Rue de Crimée. She seems quite at home in the shadow of the walls, set on a bench on the right, like everyone else on this side of the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have spent a great deal of time in these last few days, in the vicinity of the park where I was presentable. Here are the main points of departure: Paris, Bordeaux; (René) Meaux; (Georges) Paris; (André) Paris; (And Villette) Bordeaux; (And Ingeine) Bordeaux; (And Guienne) Paris. Then there is Bordeaux; (And And André) Paris; (And And Valletta) Paris; (And And Neuilly) Paris. And here is where I am just now stopping at the entrance of the Rue Lafayette, when in the fury of a long Himalayan lightning chain I can feel the relentless heat of the fury of a forest—on my right, in the heart of the reservoir where I sat, cursing the absence of water in the windows and the distant murmur of cages and lakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
I have a feeling that the world’s poor servants are not the only ones to lean on the spigot of their assumption. It is in fact quite clear that the factors who precipitate the various movements of the earth’s crust are not the only ones to go up and down, either mechanically or by means of the pendulum, but from one particular to another, as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>