<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SAIGE</title>
    <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SAIGE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://saige.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the parricide of the most important facts. It was in love that I was most obliged to return home, to a country country where I alone can now offer you my life, your tears, your tender cries, your tender pennants. The only thing I would add to your wretched eyes, those are all that remain of humanity, decency, and the most important instinct in your lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the story of the poet or of the poet who had so kindly lent his time and his talents to writing a hymn, a poem, which he passed on to his friends, even though their memory would have endorsed it. Poets always had a right to lend their time, even to lend their talents, but not to lend money. The most outstanding part of the past few months, the news of the arrest of a poet in the Armenian community, the surprise made by an order of a guild in the Swedish jurists, the abrogation of letters sent by my friend and intellectual collaborator Jarry to Philippe Soupault&#39;s house in Paris, all this compounded my griefs sorrow over the atrociousness of the facts, and the profound sincerity of the words which emerged from their mouths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker, and the one that offers the most touching reflections on the man who, in the depths of his meditation, suddenly opens his eyes and sees only the world that he has created, and who, without any restraint, does not seem to find any other world than what he is, until the moment at which it is realised that it is his reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. In the course of a trip to the Gare Saint-Lazare, for example, I happened to be looking at an old mannequin from as old as the century have certainly made her. The old mannequin had delightedly recurted from to any desire or liking. It was made of a kind that must not be forgotten, that name that, like a siren to the flowers that it had replaced, was made of a white material, that light that could not be separated from its beak, and that a head decorated with a true saint, that no reflections from an eye disfranchise us from that holy site where the most precious of human virtues are venerated with open arms: the mannequin manufactory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the parricide of the most important considerations of life. It is a pity that the advice of a psychiatrist is no longer being given to the service of which it is furnished. Psychiatrist, you are an affront to psychiatry. You have turned a blind eye to the epidemic! It is not my job to go and see it. I shall be called upon to say what has been the cause of the present disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
The first thing I do when I see a woman is to kneel beside her beloved. But if I am going to know her, I have to know her whole life. And to know her whole life with all the abandon and emotion that a decomposed woman makes, with her hair, her eyes, and her whole being. I have not only to do, but also very well do amon, I mean do an excellent, very well, wonderful, without getting lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. The most famous of these is that of Roquefort, who, on the edge of a journey through the Amazon, found himself sucked into a machine whose fumes and dust he could no longer exhale, and who, unable to get off the plane again, found himself obliged to put his hands on his knees before a mirror in order to confirm his initial belief that the sky is a vast blue drum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of adventure. I have always laughed when I saw them. And I am not the kind to let the games get in the way of my great adventure. So I am perhaps missing the mark of those who tell you to get along just fine. At least keep an open mind. The road to that great bronze throat that has just the two women&#39;s lips pursed is long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of taxi drivers passing remarkable distances on their way to and from work. It was a great sin to be an ordinary driver, and I was proud to be a victim. But I loved these anecdotes about which others would have to be sensitive, and I was not entirely ignorant. I was born to keep a straight face and to avoid simplistic opinions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker who rediscovers for a special occasion a mustard seed that smelled of spring and the Eiffel Tower. Flowers! And I was in Paris, where a little café called Lac-Hautmag was sprouting German roses. The secretaries of the German newspapers came to sit in the café. When the news broke in the autumn of &amp;lsquo;68 that the Eiffel Tower had been destroyed, I offered my hand even to the erstwhile favourites of the papers: not a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. I have always laughed when he cured a sick dog. He was so happy, so happy, until the hour came when he had to be put on a waiting train. He left on the platform, and there followed a minute and a half after which he would never leave the trembling stench of the locomotives. I have always held no recollection of these adventures, aside from the fact that they had been quite pleasant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. A fine story told with a good story, and the best part of the past year or so I have been to the office of Education of the Surrealists, where I was shown a small little board with no pictures on it which I must admit was a little dubious at the time. The board was very simple, having been handed out in a dark corner of the room and remained there lamenting the fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
The Great Exhibition of 1875-76
The Exhibition of Arts
The Great Exhibition of 1875-76
IT&#39;S AVAILABLE ONLINE
At A Time When the Future Is Unconstrained by Any Other Consequence
Art Is Not Only the Future&#39;s Future Future
But It Can Be Provided Without It
Especially Without It
The Present Time Is Hardly Enough
Especially Without It
Otherwise It Can&#39;t Be Provided Without It
Otherwise It Can&#39;t Be Provided Without It</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. A fine story told with a good story, and the best part of the past year or so, some pretty fine women come to see me. I have always wanted to talk to her, even to tell her about myself, and she is always so touching. I am so happy when I pass her by, and I would like to kiss her on the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of ordinary people who have had a frightful occasion to happen to them. I was brought up in a family of scarecrows. My father, grandfather and uncle were all so feared that they went off at once to save themselves from catastrophe. My mother, meanwhile, was so frightened by the broom-stroker she had at the time of her death that she did not ask her where the spook was, even thinking it was a bit odd that she should stick a stick in her trembling little toe when she could bite the spook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ======================================== I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. I have even written myself about his day to the day, touching on trivial subjects. At the end of one of his biographies, M. de Goncourt-Bouteille recounts, without ever actually looking at it, a letter he wrote to his friend and friend in Paris, M. Aragon, who was writing a book about magic: Dear friend, I have long since been attracted to your style of communication, in which the object of the pursuit’s miracle is presented, rather than the other way round, a number of plausible denouements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I am the one who is not a fan of the Tribunal. I have never had any great moral concerns to share about this damn thing. The fact is that it is a pretty good guild. I am not one to let too many people in at the T.V. Club. The members are paid a living like any other, but there is a tiny membership fee of just under twenty-five dollars a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always desired to be able to say what I say without having to explain it. I have always been interested in the question: what does the term &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; even mean in practice? And yet, until now, I had never heard anyone speak in such generalities about the nature of the enemy. Now there were two professors of political science who were absolutely abysmal when it came to demonizing Jew sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
The second of the three episodes of the &amp;ldquo;Veil of the Republic,&amp;rdquo; in which Surrealism succeeds in ridding the world of it, &amp;ldquo;Veil of the Republic&amp;rdquo; is as dead as its first movie, in which the moral as well as the practical importance of liberty is taught. In this terrible historical drama, which succeeds only in giving the impression of an intellectual history, &amp;ldquo;Prisoners of the World&amp;rdquo; loses without real cause a great number of qualities that make it different from the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 1 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r1-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I am a woman.
I am a woman who has closed my eyes.
I am a woman who has closed them again.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are cold.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are heavy.
All the doors of paradise slam shut.
My eyes are heavy, my shutters are heavy.
And I am a woman who has closed them again.
A man.
He is absent-minded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
The man with the long beard was standing at the entrance of the café. He made a mental note to get to the back of the building. The man with the long beard was sitting at the far end of the sidewalk. He spoke: &amp;ldquo;I have a gig, I swear. I&#39;ll have a meal out of this here. Five francs and ten florins is a good meal for a boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
I have never understood the desire of certain of those who follow me to express themselves. Desire, yes, but also a great deal more. They are looking for something specific, something that can reproduce what has already occurred, something that can be repeated, something that can be passed from one taste to another, something to be experienced by the senses. Here we are, in front of a live camera, capturing an extraordinary display of this desire: the subject is Engels&amp;rsquo; The Communist Manifesto (1875), directedquely by an avowed anti-Communist, the title The Party which Spoke (1875) given its full, unedited glory, and presented in full color, with the same organization and tactics adopted by Rigaud&#39;s and Engels&amp;rsquo; other Manifesto texts, the same dedication, the same style of poetic expression, the same methods of propaganda?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
The world’s most celebrated psychiatrist has just died. He was 80 years old. His final words to me were these: &amp;ldquo;My illness, my illness&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; If I must wait to be treated in a hospital again, I know that my fate will be in that same building. I am in the offing. I am just one day away from telling my story. I hope it is told in the manner that your mother told it to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have seen Mr. and Mrs. Newland walk from shop to shop, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose, always in the same pose. And yet, I was told, they went their separate ways. I was taught that the old lady was the last to be discovered, and that the old lady was found the next day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
There are two or three reasons why the most experienced and devoted fans of Marvel&#39;s The Avengers would not go out of their way to try and kill each other. The first is that, like Captain America, they love to compete. But they also love to compete on a huge and gratifying level. They are the savants of the universe. And they are relentless. I have never seen such a determined and devoted lover on display in my life-like time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ======================================== The sun is always on my left. I leave this area, which is only a few hundred meters from the main road. I go toward the house of the taxi-seller. He is on my right. I say: &amp;ldquo;The house on your left is yours. I&#39;ll go meet Nadja.&amp;rdquo; Nadja is waiting for me at the corner of the Rue Lafayette and the Rue de Crimée. She seems quite at home in the shadow of the walls, set on a bench on the right, like everyone else on this side of the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have spent a great deal of time in these last few days, in the vicinity of the park where I was presentable. Here are the main points of departure: Paris, Bordeaux; (René) Meaux; (Georges) Paris; (André) Paris; (And Villette) Bordeaux; (And Ingeine) Bordeaux; (And Guienne) Paris. Then there is Bordeaux; (And And André) Paris; (And And Valletta) Paris; (And And Neuilly) Paris. And here is where I am just now stopping at the entrance of the Rue Lafayette, when in the fury of a long Himalayan lightning chain I can feel the relentless heat of the fury of a forest—on my right, in the heart of the reservoir where I sat, cursing the absence of water in the windows and the distant murmur of cages and lakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.5 Run 2 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp5-r2-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
I have a feeling that the world’s poor servants are not the only ones to lean on the spigot of their assumption. It is in fact quite clear that the factors who precipitate the various movements of the earth’s crust are not the only ones to go up and down, either mechanically or by means of the pendulum, but from one particular to another, as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
We find ourselves on the quay the scene of one of those legendary cathedrals not often found in the world: the Senegalese, it may be, but the urbanaeous has never offered anything new, anything that might be termed a formal ally. In the reign of the Villa Franca, for instance, there existed a man who could hoist a Carpathian curve across the Atlantic, cross the Solomon Islands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
In a sense I&#39;m in love with that redheaded creature who sits at the foot of my bed and breathes me away. At one time it was a fern coloured pinky its colour of feverish folly. Now it&#39;s a pinky with a violet throat and a violet-coloured nose. She hangs her hair in both directions in a dishevelled bun. It&#39;s a long bun with white flaps between the sleeves and a long white oblong at the front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
I have just begun reading the Enneagrams they are composed between 1150 and 1250 B.C. They were composed between 1150 and 1250 and have, as I have indicated, some interesting parallels with earlier works, such as the Enneagram et al., from 1129-1175 (the same year as the last work I was reading) and En Procugina en la Lucha (1129-1175) (see my comment below for the latter&#39;s title and its connection with earlier En Procutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I have always thought that poetry was merely a fine little prose, punctual in its verbiage and faithful to the form. But, in my opinion, it fell short of this purpose. The prose was lacking, the prose lacking, the form lacking, the style lacking. And it still is: the stage is not quite ready. The stage is. Tito [Tristan] Rodiet&#39;s marvelous little live performance of the Policliet’s tormented night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
We are a family: grandfather, great-grandfather. We are all born to play. Born with aplomb. But we take it upon ourselves to take advantage of each other. Every night we go to sleep, we beg each other to return. And if we should beget one another in the streets, we we we&amp;ndash;we we&amp;ndash;we&amp;ndash;we&amp;ndash;we&amp;ndash;too often we fall asleep, tired of this game, this game, and that game, that heart: love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
I am a pretty blonde, so the idea of being blonde is hard to swallow. I&#39;ve had pretty blonde cheeks before, and a pink one a few years ago when I was in high school. I also had a pink eye turn on me a pretty eye just the same. But now, I&#39;ve had lips so pink I can&#39;t even put one understatement. And a mouth so pink, so red, I can see it now, almost nightmarish-blue, in a man whom I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll never meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have found a simple way of making the cracks in the walls of silence disappear. A simple light saber is stretched out on the table.
&amp;lt;|endoftext|&amp;gt;
LIKE A COLD STORM
By SUN
From the depths of silence
Alight from love that fades
From the fleeting
Through the lukewarm night
Through nothing at all
Perhaps there are other lovers
Like us
We are like you
LTE**M2t</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 1 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r1-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
A dog has just been given a try- IVM will let you know if it gets too far with its cratered interior. But before we can answer any further questions about this curious accessory, it is necessary to know exactly how long it takes for this unusual companion to arrive in the real world. And what does this leave for the management of ventures which, although they may be well-nigh attainable, can only result from this particular point of the chain of command rather by chance than of a reward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
In the days of the olden days, when lady pirates were a bit more common, pirates without a ship, and pirates who made a living off the sea, pirates without a ship, and pirates who made a life for the sea, with no plans at all, on these voyages, there were a hundred pirates of every color, and there are many with a blue life. Today, there are more pirates than ever: customs officers, heads of hair, shipwreckers, pirates who&#39;ve stolen a by stripping their foes of their beards and feathers, divers who&#39;ve left a smile on their wake, pirates who&#39;ve wrecked ships, treasure hunters, treasure hunters with their obsessions, treasure hunters who&#39;ve forgotten their saddles, treasure hunters who&#39;ve forgotten their hands, treasure hunters who&#39;ve hung their nets on the reefs, treasure hunters who&#39;ve forgotten their scales, treasure hunters who&#39;ve rented the parlours, treasure hunters who swear by a god with hearts of stone, treasure hunters who swallow pills, and treasure hunters who beat their chests with pencils.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 2 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
This is the last image I&#39;ll bring up, however, it already offers a good illustration of the kind of intervention of the Surrealist attitude which I have always found in great part to be lacking, the attitude which takes precedence over all my other ideas the attitude I have the power to call upon, having the good sense to prefer to the others. I am a burden to be carried along with me, and it is the attitude of aiming higher than I am that carries me along.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 2 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
We all know what happens when a scientist who was entrusted with discovering the universe is assassinated on the move. This scientist&#39;s life is in danger. His son is already in high school. The doctor&#39;s wife is in a foreign land and the father-in-law are in difficult physical conditions. Their son is a scientist working for a big country.* (It seems silly, however, to publish the names of parents killed in research projects; the parents must have felt obliged to do their best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 2 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
Our country is in a state of emergency, which means that the only thing that can be expected from it is that civil war break out in the north-east of France, between the Communist Party of Great Britain and Ireland and the Revue la peinture ise, which seeks to take France by force of arms. Ireland, which occupies the frontiers of both the two countries&amp;rsquo; main ports of transport, boasts one of the world&#39;s largest Communist parties, which has also been of great help to the Party of Ireland in this struggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 2 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r2-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have always loved the poetry of gestures, moreover, of PLAIN, and OF THIRST, for I regard them with a great view of amazement. As a matter of fact, I have seen these gestures, FACILITIES AND FACILITIES. These FACILITIES ARE GRAF, AND THEY ARE FREE. THEY ARE EXCELLENT. THEY WERE BEING FREE THE FIRST SEASON.
[1] G. MacMillan, Armand Breton.[2] ‘The Restaurant Grévain?], p. 45.[3] [4] A curious way of looking at it: is the word inn on the lips of the dollar bill worth the word innkeeper really all that good in this town?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ======================================== The father of the child who was raped in the street is standing in front of a gas station, raising his voice to express his sorrow. What can he do? The child whose innocence is at stake has nothing to fear from these strangers in the street who have everything to lose from him: silks skirts, black tights, and brown shoes. He carries his son into an adjacent room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
From the depths of the sea to the height of mountains the oceans rise; but between the continents man is unaware of the waves rising. They are men and women. They are like our fish &amp;hellip; In the depths man breathes &amp;hellip; In the depths man breathes. Breathes. Waves high &amp;hellip; the water will break &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; the bracelet of the waves &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; the bracelet of the wind &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; the bracelet of water &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; the water &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
The man with the long beard whose beard he stretched it like a sprinter&#39;s leg with his bare right hand and whose beard he stretched it like a sprinter&#39;s leg with his index finger. The grass has never spanned its entire right side. He stretched it so thin that his fingers were left-aligned. The man who stretched it so thin that his fingers were left-aligned with the grain of grass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
By Amie
It&#39;s not always the prettiest of flowers who are the mistresses. A certain sum of money, sometimes several tacks of furs, sometimes a hundred pence, had the good sense to believe that meadows, choked by the scent of musks, had been redelivered with song for more than fifteen years. I was at a time when these meadow maids were nothing more than rubber masks, masks so natural that the natural mirror must have wanted menial labor to preserve her charms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have never drunk a can of Gatorade before, and I don&#39;t think I&#39;ve stopped appreciating its fruit. But one mustn&#39;t stop at Gatorade. I hadn&#39;t been drinking it more some time ago, and now that I think of it, it&#39;s intoxicating. I can&#39;t stop evenicing any to me whatsoever. It&#39;s like Niagara Falls with its waterfall and all that escalation. What could it be worth while to drink water drunk immediately from a cannon, and from a cannon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
André Breton.
This place is haunted.
The corridors of power are dark.
The dead men&#39;s bodies pile up on the door of the flat.
André Jonsine&#39;s horse is the object of derision.
Large croupiers with wooden posts litter the pavements.
Some French passengers are victims of rabid dogs.
A policeman is bitten. The corpse of a policeman is the object of derision.
Some elderly people are the object of derision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have a daughter and have a very hard time imagining her spending any more than I would spend my whole life with her. But I can envisage her as a bird of burden tolerable to be held responsible for its weight. A bird of burden. So I can envisage her as well. A very fat, very thin bird. A very smart bird. Sentiment will dictate that I should have her about her age, around 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.8 Run 3 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp8-r3-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
When the child was growing up (and I&#39;m an early convert), her father was a policeman in the army. He held onto this faith by serving his country, and for this very reason, we were told he didn&#39;t go off on a great goose chase. He left his wife at this very moment, carried on his pious mission, and there we have Sybil and his little sister excelled at the world of the hustled carriage boys, the rote gossip of the village dells, the clustered innuendos of shoeblacks, while the boys of the big towns fought for each other on the earth with fierce zeal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>