<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Temperature 0.2 on SAIGE</title>
    <link>https://saige.netlify.app/tags/temperature-0.2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Temperature 0.2 on SAIGE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://saige.netlify.app/tags/temperature-0.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the parricide of the most important facts. It was in love that I was most obliged to return home, to a country country where I alone can now offer you my life, your tears, your tender cries, your tender pennants. The only thing I would add to your wretched eyes, those are all that remain of humanity, decency, and the most important instinct in your lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the story of the poet or of the poet who had so kindly lent his time and his talents to writing a hymn, a poem, which he passed on to his friends, even though their memory would have endorsed it. Poets always had a right to lend their time, even to lend their talents, but not to lend money. The most outstanding part of the past few months, the news of the arrest of a poet in the Armenian community, the surprise made by an order of a guild in the Swedish jurists, the abrogation of letters sent by my friend and intellectual collaborator Jarry to Philippe Soupault&#39;s house in Paris, all this compounded my griefs sorrow over the atrociousness of the facts, and the profound sincerity of the words which emerged from their mouths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker, and the one that offers the most touching reflections on the man who, in the depths of his meditation, suddenly opens his eyes and sees only the world that he has created, and who, without any restraint, does not seem to find any other world than what he is, until the moment at which it is realised that it is his reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. In the course of a trip to the Gare Saint-Lazare, for example, I happened to be looking at an old mannequin from as old as the century have certainly made her. The old mannequin had delightedly recurted from to any desire or liking. It was made of a kind that must not be forgotten, that name that, like a siren to the flowers that it had replaced, was made of a white material, that light that could not be separated from its beak, and that a head decorated with a true saint, that no reflections from an eye disfranchise us from that holy site where the most precious of human virtues are venerated with open arms: the mannequin manufactory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the parricide of the most important considerations of life. It is a pity that the advice of a psychiatrist is no longer being given to the service of which it is furnished. Psychiatrist, you are an affront to psychiatry. You have turned a blind eye to the epidemic! It is not my job to go and see it. I shall be called upon to say what has been the cause of the present disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
The first thing I do when I see a woman is to kneel beside her beloved. But if I am going to know her, I have to know her whole life. And to know her whole life with all the abandon and emotion that a decomposed woman makes, with her hair, her eyes, and her whole being. I have not only to do, but also very well do amon, I mean do an excellent, very well, wonderful, without getting lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. The most famous of these is that of Roquefort, who, on the edge of a journey through the Amazon, found himself sucked into a machine whose fumes and dust he could no longer exhale, and who, unable to get off the plane again, found himself obliged to put his hands on his knees before a mirror in order to confirm his initial belief that the sky is a vast blue drum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 1 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r1-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of adventure. I have always laughed when I saw them. And I am not the kind to let the games get in the way of my great adventure. So I am perhaps missing the mark of those who tell you to get along just fine. At least keep an open mind. The road to that great bronze throat that has just the two women&#39;s lips pursed is long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 1</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s1/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 1 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of taxi drivers passing remarkable distances on their way to and from work. It was a great sin to be an ordinary driver, and I was proud to be a victim. But I loved these anecdotes about which others would have to be sensitive, and I was not entirely ignorant. I was born to keep a straight face and to avoid simplistic opinions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 2</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s2/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 2 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker who rediscovers for a special occasion a mustard seed that smelled of spring and the Eiffel Tower. Flowers! And I was in Paris, where a little café called Lac-Hautmag was sprouting German roses. The secretaries of the German newspapers came to sit in the café. When the news broke in the autumn of &amp;lsquo;68 that the Eiffel Tower had been destroyed, I offered my hand even to the erstwhile favourites of the papers: not a word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 3</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s3/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 3 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. I have always laughed when he cured a sick dog. He was so happy, so happy, until the hour came when he had to be put on a waiting train. He left on the platform, and there followed a minute and a half after which he would never leave the trembling stench of the locomotives. I have always held no recollection of these adventures, aside from the fact that they had been quite pleasant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 4</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s4/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 4 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. A fine story told with a good story, and the best part of the past year or so I have been to the office of Education of the Surrealists, where I was shown a small little board with no pictures on it which I must admit was a little dubious at the time. The board was very simple, having been handed out in a dark corner of the room and remained there lamenting the fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 5</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s5/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 5 ========================================
The Great Exhibition of 1875-76
The Exhibition of Arts
The Great Exhibition of 1875-76
IT&#39;S AVAILABLE ONLINE
At A Time When the Future Is Unconstrained by Any Other Consequence
Art Is Not Only the Future&#39;s Future Future
But It Can Be Provided Without It
Especially Without It
The Present Time Is Hardly Enough
Especially Without It
Otherwise It Can&#39;t Be Provided Without It
Otherwise It Can&#39;t Be Provided Without It</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 6</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s6/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 6 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. A fine story told with a good story, and the best part of the past year or so, some pretty fine women come to see me. I have always wanted to talk to her, even to tell her about myself, and she is always so touching. I am so happy when I pass her by, and I would like to kiss her on the lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 7</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s7/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 7 ========================================
I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of ordinary people who have had a frightful occasion to happen to them. I was brought up in a family of scarecrows. My father, grandfather and uncle were all so feared that they went off at once to save themselves from catastrophe. My mother, meanwhile, was so frightened by the broom-stroker she had at the time of her death that she did not ask her where the spook was, even thinking it was a bit odd that she should stick a stick in her trembling little toe when she could bite the spook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temperature 0.2 Run 2 Sample 8</title>
      <link>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 17:45:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://saige.netlify.app/posts/temp2-r2-s8/</guid>
      <description>======================================== SAMPLE 8 ======================================== I have always loved to hear the anecdotes of the miracle-worker. I have even written myself about his day to the day, touching on trivial subjects. At the end of one of his biographies, M. de Goncourt-Bouteille recounts, without ever actually looking at it, a letter he wrote to his friend and friend in Paris, M. Aragon, who was writing a book about magic: Dear friend, I have long since been attracted to your style of communication, in which the object of the pursuit’s miracle is presented, rather than the other way round, a number of plausible denouements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>